BABYMON
Hashtag
Move
You don’t want no problems in that
Mood
너는 너무 말이 많아
Woo
빈 수레가 요란할 뿐
Boo hashtag
Hoo hashtag
Yeah yeah yeah
난 치타처럼 달려 나가
독수리처럼 날아올라
알 수 없는 끝
향해 달려가자 꿈
Everybody give me room
누가 뭐래도 I’mma do
Na na na na na na na na na
You don’t know about me
Every rose has a thorn
우린 모두 Psycho
누구나 똑같아 너나 나나
서로 다른 Psycho
모두 다 비정상 너나 나나
조금 다른 Psycho
S-s psycho s-s-s-s psycho
웃는 얼굴 뒤엔 Just a little psycho
세상처럼 돌고 도는 우린 Psycho
Tick tack toe
Playing games
I’mma kick that door
Say my name like Ruk ruk ruk
Everybody wanna be it
Shoulda woulda coulda did it
Won’t admit like
Oh I wish you would
Who misunderstood
You ain’t got a clue
Feeling like a villain chilling
Everything I’m thrilling killing
Get in where you fit in
You a psycho too
Na na na na na na na na na
You don’t know about me
Every rose has a thorn
우린 모두 Psycho
누구나 똑같아 너나 나나
서로 다른 Psycho
모두 다 비정상 너나 나나
조금 다른 Psycho
S-s psycho s-s-s-s psycho
웃는 얼굴 뒤엔 Just a little psycho
세상처럼 돌고 도는 우린 Psycho
Can you see it
강가에 비친
두 개의 달은 너와 나
오늘이 우리 마지막 밤인 것처럼
미쳐가 보자
This is for everybody
You’re not just anybody
Shout out and tell somebody
We are the psychos
This is for everybody
You’re not just anybody
Shout out and tell somebody
We are the psychos
Na na na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na
We are the psychos